Guide to the Autograph Files, 1669-1995
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- S
  - Schick, J., 1908 May 24; (1 letter)
  - Schlesinger, Arthur Jr., 1959 May 11-22; (2 letters)
  - Schmidt, Arthur Paul, 1884 Dec 6; (1 letter)
  - Schoeneman, F., 1929 Aug 22; (1 letter)
  - Schou, James, 1869 Oct 26; (1 letter)
  - Schueberg, Budd Wilson, 1935-1936; (2 letters)
  - Schumann, Robert, 1853 Jul 5; (1 letter)
  - Schumann-Heink, Ernestine, 1910 Jan 13; (1 note)
  - Schurman, Jacob Gould, 1916-1918; (2 letters)
  - Schurz, Carl, 1898 Jan 13; (1 letter)
  - Schuyler, Louisa Lee, 1899 Sep 11; (1 letter)
  - Schwartz, Delmore, 1945 Apr 3-16; (2 letters, 2 envelopes)
  - Scofield, Cora L., 1916-1951; (8 letters)
  - Scott, James Brown, 1935 May 7; (1 letter)
  - Scott, Mary Augusta, 1916 May 7; (1 letter)
  - Scott, Sarah E., [no year] Feb 20; (1 letter)
  - Scott, Sir Walter, 1819-1831; (3 letters, 1 bound collection of writings)
  - Scranton, Robert L., 1946-1947; (2 letters)
  - Scudder, Horace Elisha, 1893-1901; (3 letters)
  - Scudder, Vida DuHon, 1897-1928; (1 letter, 1 postcard)
  - Seldes, Gilbert, undated; (2 letters)
  - Seldes, Helen, 1934-1937; (15 letters, 1 postcard)
    — Includes material on anti-fascism, political and social life in New York City, country life in Vermont, and a strike by Vermont marble workers.
  - Seligman, Edwin R.A., 1927 May 31; (1 letter)
  - Sepeshy, Zoltan, 1940 Nov 5-25; (1 letter)
  - Setan, Ernest Thompson, 1907 Mar 6; (1 letter)
  - Seth, Andrew, 1896 Oct 12; (1 letter)
  - Severn, Joseph, [no year] Apr 16; (1 letter)
  - Sforza, Count Carlo, 1940; (4 letters, 2 notes, 1 essay)
  - Shakers, 1947 Aug-Sep; (2 letters)
  - Shane, Peggy, 1935; (3 letters)
  - Shattuck, Mandana M., 1854-1887; (6 letters)
  - Shaver, Dorothy, undated; (1 letter)
  - Shaw, Charlotte Frances (wife of George Bernard Shaw), 1914 Jan 3; (1 letter)
  - Shaw, Emily, 1857 Jul 20; (1 letter)
  - Shaw, George Bernard, 1914, 1935; (2 letters)
  - Shear, T. Leslie, 1927 Apr-May; (2 letters)
  - Sheeler, Charles, 1940 Nov 2-19; (1 letter)
  - Sheppard, Sarah F., 1904 Dec 10; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Shera, J. Fletcher, 1885 Aug 26; (1 letter)
  - Sherman, F.D., 1908-1916; (3 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Sherwood, Margaret, undated; (2 letters)
  - Sherwood, Mary, 1913 Aug 4; (1 letter)
  - Sherwood, Robert E., 1952 Oct 30; (1 letter)
  - Shinn, Cornelia W., 1866 May 21; (1 letter)
  - Shinn, Milicent W., 1899 Oct 2; (1 letter)
  - Shongo, Moses, 1904 Mar 18; (1 note)
  - Sidgwick, Cecily, 1914 Jan 1; (1 letter)
  - Sidgwick, Eleanor Mildred, 1900 Feb 26; (1 letter)
  - Simons, Netty, 1961-1965; (9 letters, 1 envelope, 1 postcard)
  - Sinclair, May, 1924 May 27; (1 letter, 1 note, 1 envelope)
  - Sinding, Paul Christian, 1871 Sep 30; (1 letter)
  - Singer, Charles, 1926 Jan 10; (1 letter)
  - Sitsky, Larry, 1990 Feb; (1 letter)
  - Skeel, Adelaide, 1911 Apr 14; (1 letter)
  - Skinner, Cornelia Otis, 1956 Jun 11; (1 letter)
  - Skinner, Otis, [no year] Jun 28; (1 letter)
  - Skinner, W.M., 1908 Oct 26; (1 letter)
  - Skinner, William, 1929-1931; (8 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Small, Fanny, 1864-1866; (10 letters)
    — Includes material on teaching music and social events at Vassar College.
  - Smiley, Alfred H., 1872 Mar-May; (1 letter, 1 copy)
  - Smith, Adam, 1777-1899; (2 letter copies)
  - Smith, Alfred E., 1919-1927; (9 letters, 2 envelopes, 1 newspaper clipping, 1 pamphlet)
  - Smith, B.B. (of Kentucky), 1864; (1 letter, 3 copies)
    — Includes material on incident involving a runaway slave's confrontation with his white mistress (owner).
  - Smith, George Adams, [no year] Apr 23; (1 letter)
  - Smith, Gerrit, 1852-1871; (4 letters)
  - Smith, Henry Boynton, 1875 Feb 16; (1 letter)
  - Smith, Judson, 1940 Nov 2-25; (2 letters)
  - Smith, Margaret Chase, 1958-1964; (2 letters)
  - Smith, Marguerite L., 1920 Dec 8; (1 letter)
  - Smith, Preserved, 1906 May 4; (1 letter)
  - Smith, Truman, 1848 Nov 21; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Snow, C.P., 1960 May 20; (1 letter)
  - Soderblom, Nathan, 1923 Oct 24; (1 letter, 1 scedule)
  - Soennecken, Marjorie Kudlich, 1946 Oct 14; (1 letter)
  - Somerville, E. OE., 1914 Jan 14; (1 letter)
  - Somerville, Mary, 1870-1872; (3 letters)
  - Sonneck, Oscar George, 1909-1912; (2 letters, 1 note)
  - Spafford, Jessie I., 1939 Feb-Apr; (4 letters)
  - Spargo, John, 1906 Mar 22; (1 letter)
  - Spalding, Walter Raymond, 1906 Oct 23; (1 letter)
  - Speers, Thomas Guthrie, 1920 Aug 4; (1 letter)
  - Speicher, Eugene, 1940 Nov 3-18; (2 letters)
  - Spencer, Herbert, 1894-1895; (2 letter, 1 envelope, 1 photograph)
  - Spisek, Dr. F., 1927 Oct 11; (1 letter)
  - Spontini, Gasparo, 1837-1839; (2 letters)
  - Spurgeon, Caroline, 1920 Jan-Oct; (2 letters)
  - Squire, William Barclay, 1909 Oct 7; (1 letter)
  - St. George, Katherine, 1950 May 15; (1 letter)
  - Stainer, John, 1897 Mar 23; (1 letter)
  - Stanford, Leland, 1887 Feb 16; (1 pamphlet, 1 signature clipping)
  - Stanley, Arthur Penrhym, 1880 Mar 13; (1 letter)
  - Stanton, Elizabeth P., 1885 Jul 11; (1 letter)
  - Stanton, H.B., 1871 Jun 28; (1 letter)
  - Stanton, Robert L., 1904-1914; (6 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Stanton, Theodore, 1884 Jun 10; (1 letter)
  - Starbuck, Kathryn H., 1947 Sep 23; (1 letter)
  - Stearns, Mary E., 1886-1887; (2 letters)
  - Stedman, Edmund Clarence, 1886-1907; (8 letters, 1 autographed verse)
  - Steel, F.C., 1914 Jan 9; (1 letter)
  - Stefansson, Vilhjalmur, 1928-1934; (7 letters)
  - Steinbeck, John, 1962 Nov 27; (1 letter)
  - Stepanek, Dr. Bedrich, 1923 Oct 30; (1 letter)
  - Stephens, H. Morse, 1894 Nov 25; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Stevens, Rosa Sharpe, 1938 May-Jun; (2 letters, 1 postcard)
  - Stevenson, Adlai Ewing (1835-1914), 1914 Apr 24; (1 letter, 1 pamphlet)
  - Stevenson, Adlai Ewing (1900-1965), 1952-1962; (4 letters, 1 envelope, 1 pamphlet)
  - Stevenson, E.L., 1907 Oct 14; (1 letter)
  - Stevenson, Robert Louis, circa 1894, undated; (1 manuscript poem, 1 bound manuscript) (Box 3)
  - Stewart, Donald Ogden, [no year] Mar 27; (1 letter)
  - Stewart, Marjorie, [no year] Sep 8; (1 letter)
  - Stickney, Dorothy, 1962 May 16; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Stilson, Sarah Lyra, 1865; (1 letter)
  - Stockton, Frank R., 1886-1887; (3 letters)
  - Stoddard, [C?].W., 1885 Sep 3; (1 letter)
  - Stoddard, R.L., undated; (1 poem)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1915 Jun 17; (1 letter)
  - Stolberg, Ben, 1936 Aug 3; (1 letter)
  - Storrs, Gertrude (Cleveland), 1931-1933; (4 letters)
  - Storrs, Richard Salter, 1875, 1880; (2 letters)
  - Stowe, Harriet Beecher, 1832; (1 letter, 1 photocopy)
  - Strauss, Richard, [no year] Nov 19; (1 note)
  - Street, Alfred B., 1855 Feb 14; (1 letter, 1 poem)
  - Street, Julian, 1926 Mar 11; (1 letter)
  - Strong, Ann Louise (Schulz), 1966 Mar 11; (1 letter)
  - Strong, Augustus H., 1885-1919; (1 letter)
  - Strong, Josiah, 1889 Jan 23; (1 letter)
  - Strunk, W., Jr., 1908 May 12; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Studley, Helen E., undated; (1 letter)
  - Sturgis, Russell, 1901 Jan 2; (1 letter)
  - Sugimoto, Etsu Inagaki, 1935 Dec 15; (1 letter)
  - Sumner, Charles, 1848-1868; (2 letters)
  - Swan, Cyrus, 1848-1896; (6 letters, 2 envelopes)
  - Swan, Frances W., 1900-1922; (4 letters, 1 obituary)
  - Swan, William M., 1942 May 24; (1 letter)
  - Swift, C.W., 1868 Aug 7; (1 letter)
  - Swinnerton, Frank, 1925 Jun 30; (1 letter)
  - Swisher, Carl B., 1962 Dec 28; (1 letter)
  - Symmes, Anna (Day), 1913 Jan 25; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Symons, Charles, 1812 Dec 6; (1 letter)
- T
  - Taft, Charles P., 1956 Oct 15; (1 letter)
  - Taft, Lorado, 1926 Dec 11-20; (2 letters)
  - Taft, William Howard, 1915-1916; (1 photograph, 2 letters)
  - Taggart, Genevieve, undated; (3 letters)
  - Talbot, Marion, 1897 Mar; (1 letter)
  - Talma, Louise, 1962-1963; (2 letters)
  - Taraknath, Das, 1943 Mar 4-5; (1 letter)
  - Tarchiani, Teresa, 1941 Nov 25; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Tarkington, Booth, 1921 Jun 8; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Taubes, [no year] Oct 31; (1 letter)
  - Taussig, F.W., 1916 Feb 10; (1 letter)
  - Tawney, Annette Jeanie (Mrs. Richard Henry), undated; (1 postcard)
  - Taylor, Bayard, 1862-1876; (5 letters, 2 envelopes)
  - Taylor, Charles H., 1942 Jan 24; (1 letter)
  - Taylor, Frances Henry, 1946 Oct 22; (1 letter)
  - Taylor, Helen, 1879 Oct 18; (1 letter, 1 pamphlet)
  - Taylor, Jeanette S., 1913 Jan 20; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Taylor, Kate Huntington (Mrs. James Monroe Taylor), 1917; (1 letter)
  - Taylor, Mary Atwater, 1938 Apr 17; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Taylor, Phoebe, 1936 Jul 3; (1 letter)
  - Taylor, Robert E., 1889-1893; (3 letters)
  - Teasdale, Sarah, undated; (1 letter)
  - Tebaldini, Giovanni, 1897 Jun 19; (1 letter, 1 notecard)
  - Temple, Richard, 1882 Dec 1; (1 letter)
  - Tenney, Sanborn, 1866 Nov 19; (1 letter)
  - Tenniel, John, 1876 Oct 31; (1 letter)
  - Tennyson, Lord Alfred, 1897 Nov 4; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Terry, Adolphine Fletcher, 1961 Jun 26; (1 letter)
  - Terry, Harriet W., 1877 Jun 17; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Thacher, John Boyd, 1879 Feb-May; (12 letters, 9 envelopes)
  - Thackray, Clara, 1879 Feb-Jun; (12 letters, 11 envelopes)
  - Thallon, Ida C., 1915 Sep 16; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Thayer, Julia H., undated; (1 letter)
  - Thayer, W.R., 1897-1916; (2 letters)
  - Thelberg, Elizabeth B., 1913 Jan 3; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Thielen, Helen, 1945-1951; (9 letters, 8 envelopes)
  - Thomas, Benjamin P., 1952 Dec 4; (1 letter)
  - Thomas, Lowell, 1938-1965; (4 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Thomas, M. Carey, 1889-1915; (7 letters)
    — Includes material on Bryn Mawr positions for Vassar graduates, the Association of Collegiate Alumnae, and committee positions.
  - Thomas, Norman, 1959 Nov-Dec; (2 letters)
  - Thomas, Theodore, 1897 May 23; (1 letter)
  - Thompson, C. Mildred, 1961-1967; (1 letter)
  - Thompson, Dorothy, undated; (1 photograph, 1 pamphlet excerpt, 1 [bookplate?])
  - Thompson, Frederick Ferris, 1872-1897; (9 letters)
  - Thompson, Randall, 1935-1939; (2 letters)
  - Thompson, Sidney, [no year] Jan 21; (1 letter)
  - Thorpe, Anne L., 1960 Aug 5; (1 letter)
  - Thurston, Ada, 1912-1919; (9 letters)
  - Tiffany & Co., 1903 May 20; (1 letter)
  - Tilton, Theodore, 1870-1875; (2 letters)
  - Tischner, E. Bradford, 1915 Nov 22; (1 letter)
  - Tiselius, Arne, 1949 May 19; (1 letter)
  - Tissot, James Joseph Jacques, [no year] Sep 18; (1 letter)
  - Tolstoy, Alexandra, 1959; (1 note, 1 pamphlet)
  - Tolstoy, Leo, 1896-1908; (18 letters, 20 envelopes, 1 journal, 1 postcard, 1 photograph)
    — Includes material on religion, writing, non-violence as part of Christianity, Shakers and chastity, evils of patriotism, and his health. Also includes letters from E.H. Crosby.
  - Tolstoy, Sophie, 1892-1894; (3 letters, 3 envelopes)
    — Includes material on Leo's work among the Russian peasants (in French).
  - Tomlinson, George, 1944 Apr-May; (2 letters)
  - Toscanini, Arturo, 1934 Mar 11; (1 note)
  - Tosti, Francesco Paolo, undated; (1 letter)
  - Townsend, Frederick, 1885 Jun 5; (1 letter)
  - Toynbee, Arnold J., 1947 Oct 7; (1 postcard)
  - Toynbee, Paget, 1908 Aug 10; (1 postcard)
  - Train, George Francis, 1864 May 2; (2 letters)
  - Treutlein, P., 1898 Feb 12; (1 postcard)
  - Trevelyan, George Olto, 1923 Jan-Mar; (2 letters, 2 envelopes, 1 postcard)
  - Trollope, Frances, [no year] Jul 24; (1 letter)
  - Trumball, Jonathan, undated; (1 matted photograph)
  - Tryon, Francis, 1865 Mar-Aug; (4 letters)
  - Tryon, Sylvia, 1911 Sep 6; (1 letter)
  - Tschudy, Herbert, 1934 May 29; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Turner, Joseph Mallord William, undated; (1 framed letter)
  - Tweedy, Henry H., 1921 Feb 10; (1 letter)
  - Twitchell, Robert R., 1936 Mar-May; (2 letters)
  - Tyler, Fred W., 1887 Sep 23; (1 letter)
  - Tyler, Moses Coit, 1891 Oct 5; (1 letter)
  - Tyng, Stephen H., 1875 Feb 3; (1 letter)
- U
  - Uland, Brenda, 1930-1935; (2 letters)
  - Ulisla, Parla, 1953 Nov 22; (1 letter)
  - Ulrich, Janet R., 1911 Aug 16; (1 letter)
  - Underhill, Adelaide, 1899-1927; (14 letters, 12 envelopes)
    — Includes material on Vassar College Library affairs, salaries, and some personal issues.
  - Untermeyer, Louis, 1939 Oct 31; (1 postcard)
  - Updike, Daniel Berkeley, 1923 Jan 22; (1 letter)
  - Updike, John, 1978; (1 poem)
- V
  - Vaillant, Rene, 1964 May-Jun; (2 letters)
  - Vanderbilt, Cornelius Jr., 1921 Mar 11; (1 letter)
  - Van Doren, Carl, 1923-1936; (36 letters, 13 envelopes)
    — Includes material on T.S. Eliot's poetry, Tom Boyd's death, Katherine Mansfield and Middleton Murray, publishing issues, and personal news, largely to Ruth Fitch (Mason).
  - Van Dyke, Henry, 1888-1926; (4 letters)
  - Van Ingen, Henry, 1889-1896; (7 letters, 2 notes, 1 catalogue cover)
  - Van Loon, Gerard Willem, 1959-1979; (33 letters, 36 envelopes, 22 Christmas greetings, 10 postcards, 1 pamphlet, 1 note, 1 telegram, 3 newspaper clippings, 1 book made by nephew)
  - Van Loon, Hendvik Willem, 1935; (1 letter, 4 pages newspaper clippings)
  - Van Vliet, Benson, 1893-1901; (4 letters, 2 envelopes)
  - Vassar, Albert E., 1885 Aug-Sep; (2 letters)
  - Vassar, Frank J., 1917 Apr 24; (1 letter)
  - Vassar, James W., 1848-1852; (2 letters, 5 letter copies)
  - Vassar, John Guy, 1863-1885; (3 letters)
  - Vassar, Matthew Jr., 1866-1879; (7 letters, 1 envelope, 1 leaf, 1 photocopy)
  - Vassar, William James, 1909 Jun; (1 letter copy)
  - Vaughan-Williams, Ralph, undated; (1 autograph, 1 envelope)
  - Vedder, Elihu, 1883; (1 admission ticket with autograph)
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1886 Jun 24; (1 letter)
  - Vernon, Mabel, 1950-1971; (5 letters)
  - Vignoury, Henry, 1920 Nov 23; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Villard, Fanny Garnson, 1898 Feb 20-22; (2 letters, 1 autograph)
  - Villard, Oswald Garnson, 1915-1936; (2 letters, 1 envelope, 2 copies)
  - Vincent, Sybil, 1936 Nov 2; (1 letter)
  - Viollis, Andree, 1935 Nov 26; (1 letter)
  - Voorhis, John Van, 1874 Jan 12; (1 letter)
- W
  - Wace, A.J.B, 1929 Nov 11; (1 letter)
  - Wadsworth, James W. Jr., 1922 May 2; (1 letter)
  - Wagner, Richard, 1854 May 8; (1 letter)
  - Waite, Alice V., 1918 Apr 30; (1 letter)
  - Walcott, Charles D., 1915 Dec 4; (1 letter)
  - Walker, Francis A., 1889 Oct 22; (1 letter)
  - Walker, Dr. Mary E., 1913 May 29; (1 note)
  - Wallace, Alfred R., 1886 Nov 25; (1 letter)
  - Wallace, Henry A., 1944-1946; (3 letters)
  - Wallace, Lew, 1885 Mar 27; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Wallace, Susan E., 1886 Dec 31; (1 letter, 1 envelope, 1 newspaper clipping)
  - Wallack, John Lester, 1885 Jan 3; (1 letter)
  - Wallas, Graham, 1894 Sep 26; (2 letters)
  - Walpole, Horace (1717-1797), 1796; (1 photocopied will) (Box 1)
  - Ward, Vassie (James), 1913 Jul 28; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Warde, Frederique, 1924-1929; (2 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Ware, Caroline, 1921 Mar 11; (21 letters, 3 pages of notes, 1 article copy)
  - Warner, Charles Dudley, 1873-1888; (11 letters, 4 envelopes)
  - Warren, Samuel P., 1858; (1 signed pamphlet cover)
  - Washburn, Margaret Floy, 1896-1928; (5 letters, 3 envelope)
  - Washington, Booker T., [1879?]-1901; (5 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Washington, Booker T., 1911 Jun 7; (1 framed letter) (Framed storage 1.5)
  - Washington, George, to the Hebrew Congregation of Newport, RI, 1790, undated; (1 framed letter facsimile) (Framed storage 1.5)
  - Watkins, Franklin C., 1940 Nov 22; (2 letters)
  - Watson, Thomas J, Jr., 1956 Apr 23-26; (2 letters)
  - Wayland, Francis, 1884 Nov 9; (1 letter)
  - Weaver, Peggy Wood, undated; (1 letter)
  - Webster, Daniel, 1832-1840; (1 letter, 1 note, 1 envelope)
  - Webster, Helen W., 1873-1881; (2 letters)
  - Weed, Ella, 1872 Jun 10; (1 letter)
  - Weeks, I.H., 1885 Sep 19; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Weld, Angelina Grimke, 1862; [Missing as of March 2012]
    — Includes material on her daughter attending Vassar.
  - Wellington, Anne, 1961 May 5; (1 letter)
  - Wells, David Ames, 1918 Aug 20; (1 postcard)
  - Wells, H.G., undated; (1 letter)
  - Wells, Katherine (Adams), 1936-1937; (2 letters)
  - Welsh, Elizabeth, 1887 May 19; (1 letter)
  - Welty, Eudora, 1872 Jun 10; (1 letter, 1 signed pamphlet)
  - Wemyss, Mary, 1914 Jan 10; (1 letter)
  - Wernicke, 1899 Feb-Apr; (2 letters)
  - Wey, Frances (Liggett), 1909 Oct 30; (1 letter)
  - Weyerhaeser, Elizabeth, 1911 Aug 17; (1 letter)
  - Wharton, Edith, 1916-1917; (3 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Wheeler, Everett Pepperrell, 1917 Nov 7; (1 letter)
  - Wheeler, Jessie F., 1938 Nov 18; (1 letter)
  - White, A.S., 1858 Nov 2; (1 letter)
  - White, Andrew Dickson, 1872-1890; (3 letters, 1 document)
  - White, H.L., 1891 Jan 26; (1 letter)
  - White, Helen Magill, 97 May 25; (1 letter)
  - White, James Terry, 1872 Jun 10; (1 letter, 1 pamphlet, 2 cards)
  - White, Jessie Menton, 1856 May 10; (1 letter)
  - White, Jessie Orr, 1928-1934; (5 letters, 5 envelopes)
  - White, Peter, 1906 Jan 12; (1 letter)
  - Whitely, Opal, 1922 Jun 10; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Whiting, Lilian, 1887 Jan 26; (1 letter)
  - Whitlock, Brand, 1930 Dec 27; (1 letter)
  - Whitman, Walt, 1842-1892; (1 document, 6 reprints of notes, 1 pamphlet, 1 envelope, 2 letters, 1 autobiographic note)
  - Whitney, Mary W., 1886-1914; (18 letters, 1 poem, 1 page prose, 3 envelopes, 1 page notes)
    — Includes material on Vassar College Observatory, woman's equality and men's dislike of independent women, and family and personal news.
  - Whitney, W.D., 1890 Oct 19; (1 letter)
  - Whitney, Willis R., 1926 Sep 22; (1 letter)
  - Whittier, John Greenleaf, 1867, 1880-1889, undated; (5 letters, 1 manuscript ("The Robin"), 1 envelope, 1 letter copy, 1 signed poem with photograph)
  - Wicker, Julia F., 1913 Jul 11; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Widdemer, Margaret, undated; (1 letter)
  - Wiebe, Edw, 1866 Feb-Mar; (3 letters)
  - Wight, Rezim A., 1878-1886; (3 letters, 2 postcards)
  - Wilbur, Curtis D., 1925 Apr 24; (1 letter)
  - Wilder, Thornton, 1949-1950; (6 letters, 1 envelope, 2 postcards)
    — Includes material on lecturing at Vassar, Spanish Theater, women's education, his work and research.
  - Wiley, Eliza M., 1865 Nov 2; (1 letter)
  - Willard, Emma, 1845 Oct 12; (1 letter)
  - Willard, Frances E., 1885-1895; (11 letters)
  - Wille Brandt, Mabel Walker, 1924 Apr 22; (1 letter)
  - Williams, Ben Ames, 1949 Nov 19; (1 postcard)
  - Williams, Charles D., 1914-1917; (2 letters)
  - Williams, Clark, 1936 Apr-May; (4 letters)
  - Williams, Gertrude (Frothingham), 1915 Sep 30; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Williams, Harriet (Trumbull), 1924; (1 letter, 1 card)
  - Williams, John S., 1904-1907; (1 letter)
  - Williams, Lucretia, 1910-1921; (4 letters)
  - Williams, S.G., 1891 Jan 24; (1 letter)
  - Williams, Willam Carlos, undated; (1 letter)
  - Williamson, Alice, [no year] Jan 11; (1 letter)
  - Williamson, Francis, undated; (19 letters)
  - Williamson, Louise C., 1929 Oct 2; (1 letter)
  - Willis, Frances E., 1955 Nov 22; (1 letter)
  - Willoughby, W.W., 1930-1941; (6 letters)
  - Wilson, C.W., 1894 Aug 23; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Wilson, Edmund, 1934 Apr 2; (1 letter)
  - Wilson, Ernest H., 1927-1929; (2 letters)
  - Wilson, Grace P., 1934 Mar 3; (1 letter)
  - Wilson, Mary T., 1961 Apr 29; (1 letter)
  - Wilson, Woodrow, 1886-1917; (3 letters, 7 letter copies, 1 copy of The President's War Message)
  - Wimpfheimer, Charles A., 1926 Sep 21; (1 letter)
  - Windeyer, Lady Margaret, 1911 Jan 17; (1 letter)
  - Winsor, Justin, 1889, 1994; (2 letters)
  - Wishart, C.F., 1920 Nov 17; (1 letter)
  - Witowsky, Esther, 1938-1939; (4 letters)
  - Wolcott, Fred C., 1918 Dec 20; (1 letter)
  - Wolf, Hugo, 1887 May 26; (1 letter)
  - Wolff, Leonhard, 1897 May 17; (1 letter)
  - Wood, Clement, undated; (1 letter)
  - Wood, Frances A., 1892-1904; (5 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Wood, John H., 1842-1844; [Missing as of March 2012]
    — Includes material on shoemaker apprenticeship and wages and living costs in Woburn, Mass.
  - Wood, Leonard, 1921 Jan 26; (1 letter)
  - Woodford, Stewart L., 1901 Apr 20; (1 letter)
  - Woods, M.L., 1914 Jan-Feb; (2 letters, 1 postcard)
  - Woodson, Carter G., 1929-1942; (3 letters)
  - Woodward, C. Vann, 1960 Dec 5; (1 letter)
  - Woodward, Helen, 1935-1953; (4 letters, 2 envelopes)
  - Woodward, Helen D., 1912-1932; (2 letters, 2 envelopes, 1 newspaper clipping, 1 transcript of toast at Alumnae Luncheon)
  - Woodward, W.E., 1933-1936; (4 letters)
  - Woolley, Mary E., 1904-1944; (7 letters)
  - Woolson, C.F., [1938 Oct 15?]; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Wright, Carroll D., 1888 Oct 21; (1 letter)
  - Wright, Mrs. Andrew, 1910 Jan 2; (1 letter)
  - Wright, A. Bailey, 1905 Jun 25; (2 letters)
  - Wright, D.G., 1885 Jul 8; (1 letter)
  - Wright, Frances, undated; (1 letter)
  - Wright, Helen, 1949 May 13; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Wrong, George, 1898 Feb 23; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Wroth, Lawrence, 1924 Apr 23; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Wylie, Elinor, undated; (4 letters)
  - Wylie, J.H., 1908 Feb 15; (1 letter)
  - Wylie, Laura J., 1899-1903; (2 letters, 1 envelope)
- X-Y-Z
  - Yashiro, Yukio, 1933 Jan 21; (1 letter)
  - Yerkes, Robert M., 1954-1956; (2 obituaries, 1 letter)
  - Youmans, Edward Livingston, 1875 Feb 19; (1 letter)
  - Youmans, Williams Jay, 1875 Dec 14; (1 letter)
  - Young, Charles Augustus, 1884 Oct 23, undated; (1 letter, 1 postcard)
  - Young, Henry L., 1885 May-Jul; (2 letters)
  - Young, Innis, 1944 Jan 9-11; (2 letters)
  - Young, James Hyde, 1902-1903; (3 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Young, Stark, undated; (2 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Zangwill, Mr., 1913 Dec 24; (1 letter)
  - Zeeland, Paul van, 1937 Jun 19; (1 letter)
  - Zen, Sophia (Chen), 1926-1932; (2 letters)
- Miscellaneous Autograph Books
  - Greenwood, Aaron Hobart, 1860-1861 (Box 7)
  - Platt, Hannah M., 1835-1857 (Box 7)
  - Roosevelt, Robert Brownell (?), 1871-1873 (Box 7)
  - Woodruff, Louise M. (Ithica, NY), 1866-1869 (Box 7)
  - Unidentified, 1866 (Box 7)
  - Unidentified, 1868-1870 (Box 7)